<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MEKS PORTFOLIO</string>
    <string name="goal_of_the_project">The goal of this project is to showcase our understanding and mastery of making an Android Application. When an user clicks the top left corner of the main page or slide from the left to the right, the user will find a navigation toolbar that shows each of our names. By selecting any one of the our a names, a new activity will begin taking the user to out individual profiles. In that individual profile a user can select the top right corner of that app and a menu will appear with Links to different projects posted on GitHub. When a project is selected the user will be able to open that project in Google Chrome and view the Git repository.</string>
    <string name="marisol">Marisol</string>
    <string name="eric">ERIC</string>
    <string name="krishan">KRISHAN</string>
    <string name="samer">SAMER</string>
    <string name="project_1">Project 1</string>
    <string name="project_2">Project 2</string>
    <string name="project_3">Project 3</string>
    <string name="bio_krishan">My name is Krishan Roy and I am working as a early stage Android Developer at Pursuit. You can check my projects by clicking the menu at the top right corner of the page.
        \n\n
        At this point of my life, I want to work in a growing company that makes a product, which is actually useful and not a gimmick and solves real concerns of connectivity around the world and maintains their standard.
        \n\n
I offer more than three and a half years of experience of working with community college students from Hispanic, African American, South Asian, and undocumented backgrounds as a peer math tutor and career planning facilitator. Moreover, my prior internship experience in community organizing and career planning service have helped me to hone my leadership skills and teamwork sensibilities which could be well utilized in the course of this job.
\n\n
Besides, at this stage of my life, I want to explore what I am already doing in a bigger setting and grow with an organization that has a concrete vision for the next five to ten years, plans accordingly to fulfill that vision, and tracks its progress to actualize its vision.
        \n\n
        Since my desire and the organization’s vision converges together, I can pour my heart to make colleges accessible to my struggling younger brothers in high schools, develop my mentorship skills, gather experience in the impact of digital technologies in advising and apply for a master’s program in the higher education administration after the two years\' commitment period.


    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_personal">Personal</string>
    <string name="bio_marisol">Information Technology Professional experienced in handling high-volume requests in a call center environment. CompTIA A+, and Network+ certified in addition to a solid working knowledge of troubleshooting PC\'s, peripherals and networking issues.
        Friendly and diligent, committed to providing the highest
        levels of customer service. Excellent interpersonal and
        communication skills. Fluent in Spanish.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_samer">SamerActivity</string>
    <string name="eric_bio">Experienced and goal-oriented professional with a track record of consistently meeting and exceeding organizational goals and objectives through effective use of leadership, communication, and critical analytical skills. Skilled in building healthy relationships with colleagues to maximize effectiveness of group’s outcomes as well as using creative problem solving techniques to meet organizational challenges. Motivated and ambitious individual with great interpersonal and relationship management skills.
</string>
    <string name="eric_git1">NinjaTales on Git</string>
    <string name="eric_git2">Teller Operating System on Git</string>
    <string name="eric_git3">TicTacToe on Git</string>
    <string name="samer_git1">Text Files on Git</string>
    <string name="samer_git2">Storybook on Git</string>
    <string name="samer_git3">Unit 01 Assessment on Git</string>
    <string name="samer_bio">Former servicemember and recruitment specialist with experience in the tech industry. \n
        Pragmatic and organized with a proven track record of effectively prioritizing multiple tasks and assignments in a fast-paced work environment to efficiently meet objectives. \n
        Proactive and considered to be a highly motivated employee with the capacity to learn quickly and take responsibility for my own development. \n
        Believes in building strong co-operative relationships with co-workers and clients alike. </string>
</resources>
